{
    "subject": "resource/Deliver_Us_from_Evil_(2006_film)",
    "predicate": "property/director",
    "object": "resource/Amy_J._Berg",
    "human_readable": "The director of the film 'Deliver Us from Evil' (2006) is Amy J. Berg.",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.9487747550010681,
            "question": "Who directed the film 'Deliver Us from Evil'?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.9128159880638123,
            "question": "Is Amy J. Berg a film director?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.791333019733429,
            "question": "What other films has Amy J. Berg directed?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6430695056915283,
            "question": "What year was the film 'Deliver Us from Evil' released?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6331035494804382,
            "question": "Is 'Deliver Us from Evil' a documentary or a fictional film?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6247642040252686,
            "question": "What genre is the film 'Deliver Us from Evil'?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5295813679695129,
            "question": "Has Amy J. Berg won any awards for her directing?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5226588845252991,
            "question": "Where was 'Deliver Us from Evil' filmed?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.4565296471118927,
            "question": "What are some themes explored in 'Deliver Us from Evil'?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.4260912239551544,
            "question": "What is the main subject matter of 'Deliver Us from Evil'?"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=The director of the film 'Deliver Us from Evil' (2006) is Amy J. Berg.",
            "html": "dbpedia_2725_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What are some themes explored in 'Deliver Us from Evil'?",
            "html": "dbpedia_2725_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Where was 'Deliver Us from Evil' filmed?",
            "html": "dbpedia_2725_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Has Amy J. Berg won any awards for her directing?",
            "html": "dbpedia_2725_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_2725_100.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_2725_119.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_2725_123.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_2725_19.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_2725_2.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_2725_23.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_2725_27.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_2725_45.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_2725_46.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_2725_7.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n``` \n"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```"
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n```\n\nExplanation: The documents clearly state that \"Amy J. Berg\" is an American filmmaker and that her 2006 documentary, \"Deliver Us from Evil,\" was directed by her. Therefore, the statement that Amy J. Berg is the director of the film 'Deliver Us from Evil' (2006) is supported by the provided context information."
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": " {\n      \"output\": \"yes\"\n   }"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "qwen2.5:14b": {},
        "llama3.1:70b": {}
    },
    "final_decision": 1,
    "actual_decision": 1,
    "analysis": {
        "stratum": "Less Popular",
        "topic": "-"
    },
    "errors": {}
}